(Mrs Hofstadter:)Would you like for you
and me to talk more?
(Leonard:)You know what? It's probably fine.
(Mrs Hofstadter:)In any event,
while I've had my misgivings
(Mrs Hofstadter:)about... Penny...
(Mrs Hofstadter:)...Sheldon spoke very fondly of her
(Mrs Hofstadter:)and if she is good enough for him,
(Mrs Hofstadter:)then she's good enough for me.
(Leonard:)I'm your son. What about the fact
that she's good enough for me?
(Mrs Hofstadter:)Sure.
(Leonard:)Thanks, Mom.
(Mrs Hofstadter:)Leonard, would it make
you feel better
(Mrs Hofstadter:)to hear that your mother
approved of your life choices?
(Leonard:)Yes, it would.
(Mrs Hofstadter:)Yeah, well, you should work on that.
No, Mom, it's the same guy I've gone
out with for the past two years.
(Penny(on phone):)Yeah, the scientist.
(Penny(on phone):)Well, it's complicated. I mean, he
works with lasers and atomic magnets.